Let's see if full implementation of that cue and see in order to add the elements we use, the AQ method
of it took into parameter and value and the check.
If there is equal size minus one, then the queue is full.
Otherwise, if the front equal one minus one inch were returned, the front equal to zero and increase
their rear by one and add the items at the rear equal to value and we display a math message called
inserted and we put the element that we have inserted.
Let's see that deck method at the checks.
If front equality fall to minus one.
Then the queue is empty.
We can't remove any element from this queue.
Otherwise, if it is not empty, we are deleting the item we print the deleted.
We display a message called deleted and displayed on that item that we have that in the front and we
increase front by one if front to greater than earlier than front, equal to zero and equal to minus
one.
This is that back function.
In order to display and print the cue elements, we use a method called display and a freer if what
we call minus one at the checks that print f q is empty.
Otherwise, it will create and I print RFQ elements are and throw for that element.
It starts from front and then reaching rear.
We pass through all the elements and print them by using print percentage and we specify items at position.
Hi, this is how we print the queue.
Now let's make in a main method that starts making and inserting elements, removing the elements and
displaying the elements.
So in order to check if it is not possible, an empty queue to remove the elements.
So if you execute this program and try it in your C compiler, you will get the first method execution
deck that we have.
The queue is empty.
If we include five elements, we add one two three four five.
Now the Q have the these five elements.
Remember, we are creating an array of size five.
So the six element cannot be added to be two because there.
Q is Paul, because five is the size of the array and the size of the Q and the Q only accepts five
element, if we insert the sixth element, it will display for us that Q is full now.
We called the Method Boy Method display of type void and that removes the element entered the first
example one.
So remember one two three four five?
We are removing the elements from the first in.
For a first out, OK, so it will remove one.
Now we have just four elements.
If we start by splitting it.
OK.
It's very simple.
We are creating and we have implemented these these methods and see you can test them into your C compiler.
Now let's move and see the Q implementation in Java.
The same concept.
The same.